Guide to the Richard Ledford papers, 1964-1995.
Ledford, Richard papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Richard Ledford papers, 1964-1995.
21-26-3890
Ledford 1931-
1.4 cubic feet.
Correspondence and publications, and files about the Dept. of Food Science.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence and publications
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of food science, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence and publications
SUBJECTS
Names:
Ledford, Richard Allison.1931-; Cornell University--Faculty; New York College of Agriculture Dept. of Food Science.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Collection is closed for processing.
CONTAINER LIST
- A-B, 1981-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- C-D, 1978-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- E-F, 1975-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- G, 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- G, 1982-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- G, 1982-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- H-I, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- I, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- K, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- K, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- M-N, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- O-Q, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- R-S, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- T-U, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- W, 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Deptartment of Food Science Committees, A-P, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Deptartment of Food Science Committees, R-U, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Deptartment of Food Science Committees, R-U, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Deptartment of Food Science Space Committees, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Computer Resources Committee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Curriculum Committee Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Staff Meeting Committee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Support Operations Committee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Committee on Teaching Assistants, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cooperative State Research Service Review, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Berger International Food Development Lecture and Awards Ceremony, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Berger Fund, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- CALS Dairy Industry Task Force, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Capitol Campaign Program, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- CU Focus, Food and Human Health, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- (NEDFRC) Northeast Dairy Foods Research Center Review, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- NEDFRC Board of Directors, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Planning Committee, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Dairy Research Center, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Dairy Research Center, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Master in Food Engineering - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Under Grad Food Engineering Degree, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Food Safety Lab, 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Food Venture Center, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Undergrad Food Science Convocation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Food Science/Chemical Engineering Joint Degree Program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Food Systems, Nutrition and Health Task Force, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- McCay Lectureship, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Renovation - Stocking Hall, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Taste Panel Computing, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Food Science Course Descriptions, 1989-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Honors Program Requirements and Application (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Graduate Needs Fellowship Program, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Outstanding TA Award, 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Graduate Awards, 1984-1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Graduate Student Lists, 1964-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- USDA Fellowship, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Graduate Student Meetings, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- College Bowl Competition, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Grad Student Teaching Program - CALS, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Graduate Student Symposium, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey Assistantships, 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Expanding Your Horizons Conference, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 4-H Focus for Teens, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Summer Session, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Correspondence with Students, 1978-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Freshman Orientation, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Letters to Seniors, 1982-1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Laboratory Exercises in Food Microbiology, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)